

# JOHAN **MEDINA**

# **CONTACT**



(+57) 316 532 5256

isebastianm1113@gmail.com

bit.ly/JMdesigner

# **FOLLOW ME**

Be behance.net/jsebastianfa54

in bit.ly/linkedinJohanM

github.com/johan1113

# **LANGUAGE**

SPANISH: Native

ENGLISH: B2

# **TOOLS**

Figma Invision

Mendeley Adobe Suite

Github React

Sass Fierbase

Mongo DB Android

Wordpress Arduino

Slack Asana



# **ABOUT ME**

I am an interactive media design student whit experience in the planning, execution and development of digital products through design; achieving high levels of innovation in the market through UX Research, User Interface Design (UI) and Front-End Development.

Thanks to my professional Studies, I have developed leadership, project management, effective communication, group work and entrepreneurship skills. All together has facilitated my ability to lead and / or be part of innovation projects in real companies.



# **EDUCATION**

#### > INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

Aug 2015 - Nowadays

ICESI University, Santiago de Cali, Colombia



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### > USER INTERFACE DESIGNER (WEB)

Aug 2019 - Nowadays

#### Angular Diseño más Interacción - UI Designer & Wordpress Developer

Responsible for the design and construction of user interface content. Execution of virtual prototypes and development of interactive web platforms with Wordpress.

# > WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

#### A Creative Work - UI Designer & Wordpress Developer

Responsable for design of user interfaces for Digital Agencies, and development of web platforms with Wordpress.

### > ACADEMIC CONSULTANT - PROGRAMMING

Sept 2018 - Jun 2019

#### **Icesi University**

Advisor in the development of digital products with tools like Java, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Android, Arduino and React. Giving support to all of the Interactive Media Design Students about algorithm programming and implementation strategies.

#### > DESIGN MANAGER - GÜINEV

Jan 2018 - Jul 2020

#### **Icesi University**

Manager and councilor of the design department of Interactive Media Design students group, contributing to the creation of illustrative strategies for the design profile of this major, at national and international level through events and transmedia concepts.



# **SKILLS**

UX DESIGN PROTOTYPE DESIGN

UI DESIGN HUMAN AND COMPUTER INTERACTION

UI DEVELOPMENT INFORMATION ARQUITECTURE

DESIGN RESEARCH EXPERIMENT DESIGN THROUGH STATISTICS